Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XLVI is arranged in 51 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XLVI. GRAND LODGE
  - Sub-Series 298-0. Grand Lodge. General
    - General, 1934-1960 (Box 482, Folder 1)
    - General, 1923-1930 (Box 482, Folder 2)
    - General, 1925 (Box 482, Folder 3)
    - General, 1921-1922 (Box 482, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 298-1. Grand Lodge. General Fund
    - General Fund, 1949 (Box 482, Folder 5)
    - General Fund, 1924-1931 (Box 482, Folder 6)
    - General Fund, 1925 (Box 482, Folder 7)
    - General Fund, 1921-1922 (Box 482, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 298-2. Grand Lodge. Convention Fund
    - Convention Fund, 1934-1949 (Box 482, Folder 9)
    - Convention Fund, 1924-1927 (Box 482, Folder 10)
    - Convention Fund, 1925 (Box 482, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 298-3. Grand Lodge. Protective Fund
    - Protective Fund, 1923-1929 (Box 482, Folder 12)
    - Protective Fund, 1925 (Box 482, Folder 13)
    - Protective Fund, 1921-1922 (Box 482, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 298-5. Grand Lodge. Accounts
    - Accounts, 1929-1939 (Box 482, Folder 15)
    - Accounts, 1922 (Box 482, Folder 16)
    - Accounts. Audit Report, 1924 (Box 482, Folder 17)
      1924 December 31
  - Sub-Series 298-6. Grand Lodge. Passwords
    - Passwords, 1925-1926 (Box 482, Folder 18)
    - Passwords, 1921-1922 (Box 482, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 298-7. Grand Lodge. Vice Grand Presidents' Districts
    - Vice Grand Presidents' Districts, 1922-1928 (Box 482, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 298-8. Grand Lodge. Instructions to System Boards and Local Lodges
    - Instructions to System Boards and Local Lodges, 1923-1931 (Box 482, Folder 21)
    - Instructions to System Boards and Local Lodges, 1925 (Box 482, Folder 22)
    - Instructions to System Boards and Local Lodges, 1922 (Box 482, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 298-9. Grand Lodge. Financial Statements
    - Financial Statements, 1926 (Box 482, Folder 24)
    - Financial Statements, 1924-1925 (Box 482, Folder 25)
    - Financial Statements, 1922 (Box 482, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 298-10. Grand Lodge. Special Fund for Financial Assistance to Chesapeake and Ohio Strikers
    - Special Fund for Financial Assistance to Chesapeake and Ohio Strikers, 1923 (Box 482, Folder 27)
    - Special Fund for Financial Assistance to Chesapeake and Ohio Strikers, 1922 (Box 482, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 298-11. Grand Lodge. Traveling Cards
    - Traveling Cards, 1923-1927 (Box 482, Folder 29)
    - Traveling Cards, 1925 (Box 482, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 298-12. Grand Lodge. Assessments
    - Assessments, 1929-1931 (Box 482, Folder 31)
    - Assessments, 1930 (Box 482, Folder 32)
    - Assessments, 1929 (Box 482, Folder 33-34)
    - Assessments, 1928 (Box 482, Folder 35)
    - Assessments, 1923-1924 (Box 482, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 298-13. Grand Lodge. Applications for Auditing Books and Accounts
    - Applications for Auditing Books and Accounts, 1924 (Box 482, Folder 37)
    - Applications for Auditing Books and Accounts, 1925 (Box 482, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 298-14. Grand Lodge. Membership by Vice Grand Presidents' Districts
    - Membership by Vice Grand Presidents' Districts, 1924-1929 (Box 482, Folder 39)
    - Membership by Vice Grand Presidents' Districts, 1925 (Box 482, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 298-15. Grand Lodge. Proposed Building and Loan Department
    - Proposed Building and Loan Department, 1924 (Box 482, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 298-16. Grand Lodge. Disbursement of Funds
    - Disbursement of Funds, 1928-1940 (Box 482, Folder 42)
    - Disbursement of Funds, 1925 (Box 482, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 298-17. Grand Lodge. Organization Fund
    - Organization Fund, 1925-1928 (Box 482, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 298-18. Grand Lodge. Budget
    - Budget, 1962-1963 (Box 483, Folder 1)
    - Budget, 1960-1961 (Box 483, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 1955-1959 (Box 483, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1952-1954 (Box 483, Folder 4)
    - Budget, 1964 (Box 483, Folder 5)
    - Budget, 1948-1951 (Box 483, Folder 6)
      February 1948-51.
    - Budget, 1940-1948 (Box 483, Folder 7)
      1940-January 1948.
    - Budget, 1932-1939 (Box 483, Folder 8)
    - Budget, 1925-1931 (Box 483, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 298-19. Grand Lodge. Express Division
    - Express Division, 1925 (Box 483, Folder 10-11)
    - Express Division, 1926-1929 (Box 483, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 298-20. Grand Lodge. Insured Banking Plan
    - Insured Banking Plan, 1925 (Box 483, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 298-21. Grand Lodge. Donated Funds
    - Donated Funds, 1926 (Box 483, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 298-22. Grand Lodge. Per Capita Tax
    - Per Capita Tax, 1926 (Box 483, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 298-23. Grand Lodge. Mail
    - Mail, 1926 (Box 483, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 298-24. Grand Lodge. Group Insurance
    - Group Insurance, 1928-1929 (Box 483, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 298-25. Grand Lodge. Inventory
    - Inventory, 1932-1950 (Box 483, Folder 18)
    - Inventory, 1926-1931 (Box 483, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 298-26. Grand Lodge. Sickness and Accident Insurance
    - Sickness and Accident Insurance, 1931 (Box 483, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 298-27. Grand Lodge. Applications for Membership
    - Applications for Membership, 1928-1935 (Box 483, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 298-28. Grand Lodge. Company Union Fund
    - Company Union Fund, 1928-1931 (Box 483, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 298-29. Grand Lodge. Special Membership Reports
    - Special Membership Reports, 1928 (Box 483, Folder 23)
    - Special Membership Reports, 1929 (Box 483, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 298-30. Grand Lodge. Research Department
    - Research Department, 1930-1935 (Box 483, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 298-31. Grand Lodge. Fluctuations in Membership
    - Fluctuations in Membership. Graphic Charts, 1928-1930 (Box 483, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 298-34. Grand Lodge. The Railway Clerk
    - The Railway Clerk, 1933 (Box 483, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 298-36. Grand Lodge. Employment of Assistant General Auditors
    - Employment of Assistant General Auditors, 1931 (Box 483, Folder 28)
    - Employment of Assistant General Auditors, 1939-1940 (Box 483, Folder 29)
    - Employment of Assistant General Auditors, 1932 (Box 483, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 298-37. Grand Lodge. Death Benefit Department Fund
    - Death Benefit Department Fund, 1937-1953 (Box 483, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 298-38. Grand Lodge. Accounting Reports
    - Accounting Reports, 1934 (Box 483, Folder 32)
    - Accounting Reports, 1932 (Box 483, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 298-39. Grand Lodge. Investment of Funds
    - Investment of Funds, 1961-1963 (Box 483, Folder 34)
    - Investment of Funds, 1951-1957 (Box 484, Folder 1)
    - Investment of Funds, 1944-1950 (Box 484, Folder 2)
    - Investment of Funds, 1934-1943 (Box 484, Folder 3)
    - Investment of Funds, 1932 (Box 484, Folder 4)
    - Investment of Funds, 1931 (Box 484, Folder 5)
    - Investment of Funds, 1958-1960 (Box 484, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 298-40. Grand Lodge. Auditing and Bonding Department
    - Auditing and Bonding Department, 1932 (Box 484, Folder 7)
    - Auditing and Bonding Department, 1956-1959 (Box 484, Folder 8)
      1956-November 1959.
    - Auditing and Bonding Department, 1933-1955 (Box 484, Folder 9)
    - Auditing and Bonding Department, 1931 (Box 484, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 298-41. Grand Lodge. Special Assessment for Protective Fund
    - Special Assessment for Protective Fund, 1932-1933 (Box 484, Folder 11)
      August 1932-33.
    - Special Assessment for Protective Fund, 1932 (Box 484, Folder 12)
      April-June 1932.
    - Special Assessment for Protective Fund, 1931-1932 (Box 484, Folder 13)
      December 1931-March 1932.
    - Special Assessment for Protective Fund, 1932 (Box 484, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 298-42. Grand Lodge. Brotherhood Colors
    - Brotherhood Colors, 1948 (Box 484, Folder 15)
    - Brotherhood Colors, 1932 (Box 484, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 298-43. Grand Lodge. Austerity Measures
    - Austerity Measures, 1932-1933 (Box 484, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 298-44. Grand Lodge. Commission to Special Organizers
    - Commission to Special Organizers, 1932-1934 (Box 484, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 298-45. Grand Lodge. Attorneys
    - Attorneys, 1933-1937 (Box 484, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 298-47. Grand Lodge. Special Representatives
    - Special Representatives, 1933-1959 (Box 484, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 298-48. Grand Lodge. Total Membership
    - Total Membership, 1934 (Box 484, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 298-49. Grand Lodge. Twenty-five Year Membership Buttons
    - Twenty-five Year Membership Buttons, 1934-1938 (Box 484, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 298-51. Grand Lodge. Finance Committee
    - Finance Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 484, Folder 23)
      September 21, 1954-June 1955.
    - Finance Committee, 1954 (Box 484, Folder 24)
      March 1954-September 20, 1954.
    - Finance Committee, 1953 (Box 484, Folder 25)
    - Finance Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 484, Folder 26)
      June 1953-February 1954.
    - Finance Committee, 1952 (Box 484, Folder 27)
    - Finance Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 485, Folder 1)
      July 1952-June 1953.
    - Finance Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 485, Folder 2)
    - Finance Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 485, Folder 3)
      September 1951-June 1952.
    - Finance Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 485, Folder 4)
      September 1950-August 1951.
    - Finance Committee, 1950 (Box 485, Folder 5)
      January-August 1950.
    - Finance Committee, 1949 (Box 485, Folder 6)
      February-December 1949.
    - Finance Committee, 1949 (Box 485, Folder 7)
    - Finance Committee, 1947-1949 (Box 485, Folder 8)
      June 1947-January 1949.
    - Finance Committee, 1947 (Box 485, Folder 9)
    - Finance Committee, 1947 (Box 485, Folder 10)
      January-May 1947.
    - Finance Committee, 1946 (Box 485, Folder 11)
    - Finance Committee, 1945-1946 (Box 485, Folder 12)
    - Finance Committee, 1945 (Box 485, Folder 13)
    - Finance Committee, 1944 (Box 485, Folder 14)
    - Finance Committee, 1943 (Box 485, Folder 15)
    - Finance Committee, 1941-1944 (Box 485, Folder 16)
    - Finance Committee, 1935-1940 (Box 486, Folder 1)
    - Finance Committee. Meeting, 1957 (Box 486, Folder 2)
      1957 August
    - Finance Committee. Meeting, 1967 (Box 486, Folder 3)
    - Finance Committee. Meeting, 1966 (Box 486, Folder 4)
    - Finance Committee. Meetings, 1962-1963 (Box 486, Folder 5)
      August 1963, February 1963, November 1962.
    - Finance Committee. Meeting, 1966 (Box 486, Folder 6)
    - Finance Committee. Meeting, 1965 (Box 486, Folder 7)
    - Finance Committee. Meeting, 1965 (Box 486, Folder 8)
    - Finance Committee. Meeting, 1964 (Box 486, Folder 9)
    - Finance Committee. Meeting, 1964 (Box 486, Folder 10)
    - Finance Committee. Meeting, 1962-1962 (Box 486, Folder 11)
      August 1962, February 1962.
    - Finance Committee. Meeting, 1961 (Box 486, Folder 12)
      1961 August
    - Finance Committee. August 18, 1960-February 1961 (Box 487, Folder 1)
    - Finance Committee. March 23, 1960-August 17, 1960 (Box 487, Folder 2)
    - Finance Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 487, Folder 3)
      September 1959-March 22, 1960.
    - Finance Committee, 1959 (Box 487, Folder 4)
      January-August 1959.
    - Finance Committee, 1958 (Box 487, Folder 5)
    - Finance Committee, 1957 (Box 487, Folder 6)
    - Finance Committee, 1957-1958 (Box 487, Folder 7)
    - Finance Committee, 1956 (Box 487, Folder 8)
    - Finance Committee, 1956 (Box 487, Folder 9)
      February 8, 1956-December 1956.
    - Finance Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 487, Folder 10)
      July 1955-February 7, 1956.
    - Finance Committee, 1955 (Box 487, Folder 11)
    - Legal Department, 1944-1964 (Box 487, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 298-56. Grand Lodge. Labor Educational Department.
    - Labor Educational Department. General, 1965-1968 (Box 487, Folder 13)
      1965-August 1968.
    - Labor Educational Department. General, 1963-1964 (Box 487, Folder 14)
    - Labor Educational Department. General, 1961-1962 (Box 488, Folder 1)
    - Labor Educational Department. General, 1958-1960 (Box 488, Folder 2)
    - Labor Educational Department. Comments on Conferences, 1947-1948 (Box 488, Folder 3)
      July 1947-July 1948.
    - Labor Educational Department. General, 1947-1950 (Box 488, Folder 4)
    - Labor Educational Department. Regional Educational Directors, 1947-1949 (Box 488, Folder 5)
    - Labor Educational Department. Comments on Conferences, 1948-1949 (Box 488, Folder 6)
      September 1948-May 1949.
    - Labor Educational Department. General, 1957 (Box 488, Folder 7)
      February-December 1957.
    - Labor Educational Department. General, 1956-1957 (Box 488, Folder 8)
      1956-January 1957.
    - Labor Educational Department. General, 1954-1955 (Box 488, Folder 9)
      May 1954-55.
    - Labor Educational Department. General, 1951-1954 (Box 488, Folder 10)
      November 1951-April 1954.
    - Labor Educational Department. General, 1950-1951 (Box 488, Folder 11)
      October 1950-October 1951.
    - Labor Educational Department. General, 1949-1950 (Box 488, Folder 12)
      November 1949-September 1950.
    - Labor Educational Department. General, 1949 (Box 488, Folder 13)
      February 15, 1949-October 1949.
    - Labor Educational Department. General, 1947-1948 (Box 488, Folder 14)
      1947-February 1948.
    - Labor Educational Department. General, 1948-1949 (Box 489, Folder 1)
      March 1948-February 14, 1949.
    - Labor Educational Department. Instructional Manual (Box 489, Folder 2)
      not dated.
    - Labor Educational Department. Movie, 1950-1957 (Box 489, Folder 3)
    - Labor Educational Department. Movie, 1947-1949 (Box 489, Folder 4)
    - Labor Educational Department. Goodwin, H.L., Regional Educational Director, 1950-1952 (Box 489, Folder 5)
      November 23, 1950-52.
    - Labor Educational Department. Goodwin, H.L., Regional Educational Director, 1950 (Box 489, Folder 6)
      November 3-22, 1950.
    - Labor Educational Department. Goodwin, H.L., Regional Educational Director, 1950 (Box 489, Folder 7)
      August 1950-November 2, 1950.
    - Labor Educational Department. Goodwin, H.L., Regional Educational Director, 1950 (Box 489, Folder 8)
      June-July 1950.
    - Labor Educational Department. Goodwin, H.L., Regional Educational Director, 1950 (Box 489, Folder 9)
      March-May 1950.
    - Labor Educational Department. Goodwin, H.L., Regional Educational Director, 1949-1950 (Box 489, Folder 10)
      November 16, 1949-February 1950.
    - Labor Educational Department. Goodwin, H.L., Regional Educational Director, 1930-1949 (Box 489, Folder 11)
      August 1930-November 15, 1949.
    - Labor Educational Department. Goodwin, H.L., Regional Educational Director, 1949 (Box 489, Folder 12)
      May 7, 1949-August 29, 1949.
    - Labor Educational Department. Goodwin, H.L., Regional Educational Director. Conference Reports, 1949 (Box 489, Folder 13)
    - Labor Educational Department. Goodwin, H.L., Regional Educational Director, 1949 (Box 489, Folder 14)
      January 1949-May 6, 1949.
    - Labor Educational Department. Goodwin, H.L., Regional Educational Director. Conference Reports, 1948 (Box 489, Folder 15)
    - Labor Educational Department. Goodwin, H.L., Regional Educational Director, 1948 (Box 490, Folder 1)
      1948 December
    - Labor Educational Department. Goodwin, H.L., Regional Educational Director, 1948 (Box 490, Folder 2)
      June-November 1948.
    - Labor Educational Department. Haines, J.B., Regional Educational Director, 1949 (Box 490, Folder 3)
      September-November 1949.
    - Labor Educational Department. Haines, J.B., Regional Educational Director, 1949-1952 (Box 490, Folder 4)
      December 1949-52.
    - Labor Educational Department. Haines, J.B., Regional Educational Director, 1949 (Box 490, Folder 5)
      March-August 1949.
    - Labor Educational Department. Haines, J.B., Regional Educational Director. Conference Reports, 1949 (Box 490, Folder 6)
    - Labor Educational Department. Haines, J.B., Regional Educational Director, 1948-1949 (Box 490, Folder 7)
      December 14, 1948-February 1949.
    - Labor Educational Department. Haines, J.B., Regional Educational Director. Conference Reports, 1948 (Box 490, Folder 8)
    - Labor Educational Department. Haines, J.B., Regional Educational Director, 1948 (Box 490, Folder 9)
      September 1948-December 13, 1948.
    - Labor Educational Department. Haines, J.B., Regional Educational Director, 1948 (Box 490, Folder 10)
      June-August 1948.
    - Labor Educational Department. Haines, J.B., Regional Educational Director, 1948 (Box 490, Folder 11)
      January-May 1948.
    - Labor Educational Department. Haines, J.B., Regional Educational Director. Conference Reports, 1947 (Box 490, Folder 12)
      September-December 1947.
    - Labor Educational Department. Haines, J.B., Regional Educational Director, 1947 (Box 490, Folder 13)
    - Labor Educational Department. Kief, C.E., Regional Educational Director, 1948 (Box 490, Folder 14)
      July-December 1948.
    - Labor Educational Department. Kief, C.E., Regional Educational Director, 1948 (Box 490, Folder 15)
      April 21, 1948-June 1948.
    - Labor Educational Department. Kief, C.E., Regional Educational Director, 1947-1948 (Box 490, Folder 16)
      December 10, 1947-April 20, 1948.
    - Labor Educational Department. Kief, C.E., Regional Educational Director, 1947 (Box 491, Folder 1)
      July 1947-December 9, 1947.
    - Labor Educational Department. Kief, C.E., Regional Educational Director. Conference Reports, 1947 (Box 491, Folder 2)
      August-December 1947.
    - Labor Educational Department. Erickson, L.M., Regional Educational Director, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 3)
    - Labor Educational Department. Erickson, L.M., Regional Educational Director. Conference Reports, 1949 (Box 491, Folder 4)
    - Labor Educational Department. Erickson, L.M., Regional Educational Director, 1948-1949 (Box 491, Folder 5)
    - Labor Educational Department. Erickson, L.M., Regional Educational Director. Conference Reports, 1948 (Box 491, Folder 6)
    - Labor Educational Department. Crawford, W.M., Regional Educational Director, 1948-1949 (Box 491, Folder 7)
      July 1948-49.
    - Labor Educational Department. Crawford, W.M., Regional Educational Director, 1948 (Box 491, Folder 8)
      January-June 1948.
    - Labor Educational Department. Crawford, W.M., Regional Educational Director. Conference Reports, 1947 (Box 491, Folder 9)
    - Labor Educational Department. Crawford, W.M., Regional Educational Director, 1947 (Box 491, Folder 10)
    - Labor Educational Department. St. John, A.R., Regional Educational Director, 1950-1952 (Box 491, Folder 11)
      November 18, 1950-52.
    - Labor Educational Department. St. John, A.R., Regional Educational Director, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 12)
      July 1950-November 17, 1950.
    - Labor Educational Department. St. John, A.R., Regional Educational Director, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 13)
      May-June 1950.
    - Labor Educational Department. St. John, A.R., Regional Educational Director, 1950 (Box 491, Folder 14)
      January 24-April 1950.
    - Labor Educational Department. St. John, A.R., Regional Educational Director, 1949-1950 (Box 491, Folder 15)
      October 1949-January 23, 1950.
    - Labor Educational Department. St. John, A.R., Regional Educational Director, 1950 (Box 492, Folder 1)
      June-September 1950.
    - Labor Educational Department. St. John, A.R., Regional Educational Director. Conference Reports, 1949 (Box 492, Folder 2)
    - Labor Educational Department. St. John, A.R., Regional Educational Director, 1948-1949 (Box 492, Folder 3)
      December 1948-May 1949.
    - Labor Educational Department. St. John, A.R., Regional Educational Director, 1948 (Box 492, Folder 4)
    - Labor Educational Department. St. John, A.R., Regional Educational Director. Conference Reports, 1948 (Box 492, Folder 5)
    - Labor Educational Department. St. John, A.R., Regional Educational Director, 1948 (Box 492, Folder 6)
    - Labor Educational Department. St. John, A.R., Regional Educational Director. Conference Reports, 1947 (Box 492, Folder 7)
    - Labor Educational Department. St. John, A.R., Regional Educational Director, 1947 (Box 492, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 298-57. Grand Lodge. Special Assessment of Five Dollars
    - Special Assessment of Five Dollars, 1950-1953 (Box 492, Folder 9)
      June 1950-53.
    - Special Assessment of Five Dollars. Appeal of Lodge No. 1254, 1949-1951 (Box 492, Folder 10)
    - Special Assessment of Five Dollars, 1949-1950 (Box 492, Folder 11)
      November 1949-May 1950.
    - Special Assessment of Five Dollars, 1949 (Box 492, Folder 12)
      September-October 1949.
    - Special Assessment of Five Dollars, 1949 (Box 492, Folder 13)
      August 7-31, 1949.
    - Special Assessment of Five Dollars, 1949 (Box 492, Folder 14)
      July 26, 1949-August 6, 1949.
    - Special Assessment of Five Dollars, 1949 (Box 492, Folder 15)
      June 24, 1949-July 25, 1949.
    - Special Assessment of Five Dollars, 1949 (Box 492, Folder 16)
      June 8-23, 1949.
    - Special Assessment of Five Dollars, 1949 (Box 492, Folder 17)
      May 25, 1949-June 7, 1949.
    - Special Assessment of Five Dollars, 1949 (Box 493, Folder 1)
      May 1-14, 1949.
    - Special Assessment of Five Dollars, 1949 (Box 493, Folder 2)
      April 12-30, 1949.
  - Sub-Series 298-58. Grand Lodge. Officers' and Employees' Group Life Insurance
    - Officers' and Employees' Group Life Insurance, 1956-1957 (Box 493, Folder 3)
      March 1956-April 2, 1957.
  - Sub-Series 298-60. Grand Lodge. Diorama Exhibit
    - Diorama Exhibit, 1952-1959 (Box 493, Folder 4)
    - Diorama Exhibit, Colorado State Fair, Pueblo, Colorado, 1960 (Box 493, Folder 5)
      August 22-27, 1960.
  - Sub-Series 298-61. Grand Lodge. Speeches of the Grand President
    - Speeches of the Grand President. General Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 493, Folder 6)
      August 1959-October 1962.
    - Speeches of the Grand President, 1959-1960 (Box 493, Folder 7)
      1959-October 24, 1960.
    - Speeches of the Grand President, 1958 (Box 493, Folder 8)
      March-December 1958.